Guide to the Ship Scalers, Dry Dock, and Boat Yard Workers Union, Local 541 (Seattle, Washington) Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Ship Scalers, Dry Dock, and Boat Yard Workers Union, Local 541 (Seattle, Washington) Records, 1939-1991; 4571-001; 16 cubic feet 16 boxes
  - Series VI: Legal Files, 1943-1991 (Box-folder 7/61-11/36)
    - Subseries B: Legal Conflicts with the Laborers International Union of North America, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 8/9-8/30)
      - Notes: Negotiations with International Union, 1986 (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Leaflets and Meeting Announcements: Issues Between Local 541 and International Union, 1986 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Notes and Correspondence: Forced Merger: Transfer of Members and Officers to Local 252, 1986 (Box-folder 8/25)
      - May Day Letter for Reconsideration of Charter Revocation from Membership to International General President Angelo Fosco, 1986 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - Correspondence from International Union, 1986 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Letter Revoking Local Charter from International General President Angelo Fosco, 1986 (Box-folder 8/28)
      - Correspondence from Local 541 to International Union, 1986 (Box-folder 8/29)
      - Correspondence to Rick Ricks from Robert A. Barnes: International Takeover of Local 541, 1986 (Box-folder 8/30)
    - Subseries C: Oscar Hearde Legal Files, 1962-1986 (Box-folder 8/31-9/25)
      - Legal Documents: Pleadings and Trial Records: Case No. C81-334M (1 of 3), 1962-1981 (Box-folder 8/31)
      - Legal Documents: Pleadings and Trial Records: Case No. C81-334M (2 of 3), 1962-1981 (Box-folder 8/32)
      - Legal Documents: Pleadings and Trial Records: Case No. C81-334M (3 of 3), 1962-1981 (Box-folder 8/33)
      - Plaintiffs' Exhibits: Case No. C81-334M, 1972-1981 (Box-folder 8/34)
      - Legal Notes: Oscar Hearde, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 8/35)
      - Legal Documents and Correspondence: Oscar Hearde's Disability Retirement and Related Labor and Industries Claim, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 8/36)
      - Indexes to Depositions: Hearde and Barnes v. International, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 8/37)
      - Hearings, Correspondence, and Defendants' Exhibits: Case No. C81-334M, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8/38)
      - Legal Notes and Memoranda: Oscar Hearde, Kenneth A. MacDonald, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 8/39)
      - Press, Notes, and Memoranda: Oscar Hearde, Kenneth A. MacDonald, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8/40)
      - Correspondence between Bob Barnes, Oscar Hearde, and Kenneth A. MacDonald: Case No. C81-334M: Exhibit 18, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8/41)
      - Prehearing Order and Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law: Case No. C81-334M, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 8/42)
      - Press Release Regarding Case No. C81-334M, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8/43)
      - Special Hearings Panel: Transcript of Hearing on Oscar Hearde Elections Eligibility: May 14, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/44)
      - Deposition and Related Documents: Yvonne Quiroga: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/45)
      - Deposition and Related Documents: Oscar Hearde: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/46)
      - Deposition and Related Documents: Lawrence A. Oertli: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/47)
      - Deposition and Related Documents: John H. Tannyhill: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/48)
      - Deposition and Related Documents: Edwina Fields: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/49)
      - Deposition and Related Documents: Mason Warren: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/50)
      - Deposition and Related Documents: Luston House: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/51)
      - Deposition and Related Documents: Joel David Weigert: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/52)
      - Deposition and Related Documents: Mason Warren: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/53)
      - Deposition and Related Documents: Van T. Harrison: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 8/54)
      - Legal Documents, Correspondence, and Related Documentation: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8/55)
      - Correspondence: Executive Board Meeting Regarding Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Correspondence, Notes, and Legal Documents: Case No C81-334M, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Correspondence and Legal Documents: Case No C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Legal Document: Oral Examination Before Trial of Oscar Hearde: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Legal Document: Deposition Upon Oral Examination of Edwina Fields: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Affidavit of John Caughlan: Oscar Hearde's Attorney, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Legal Document: Deposition Upon Oral Examination of Joel Wiegert: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Legal Document: Oral Examination Before Trial of John H. Tannyhill: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Legal Document: Oral Examination Before Trial of Joel Wiegert: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Legal Documents and Correspondence: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Second Amended Complaint and Related Exhibits and Correspondence: Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Petitions by Membership in Support of Oscar Hearde: Federal Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Depositions: Court Case No. C81-334M, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Affidavit of John Caughlan: Oscar Hearde's Attorney, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Legal Correspondence and Documentation: Claims of House, Scott, Agtuga vs. Hearde/Barnes et al., 1982-1982 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Signed Agreement between International Union, Local 541 Executive Board, and Oscar Hearde: Case No. C81-334M, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Draft Proposals: Agreement between International Union, Local 541 Executive Board, and Oscar Hearde: Case No. C81-334M, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Correspondence and Litigation Dismissal: Case NO. C81-334M, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - Correspondence between Bob Barnes/Nancy San Carlos and International Union Regarding Retiree Benefits and Oscar Hearde Situation, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Resignation from Case No. C81-334M by Kenneth A. MacDonald, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 9/20)
      - Legal Documents and Correspondence: Conclusion of Case No. C81-334M, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 9/21)
      - Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law: Case No. C81-334M, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 9/22)
      - Legal Response to Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law: Case No. C81-334M, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 9/23)
      - Notes on Meetings with Legal Counsel: McGovern's Decision on Case No. C81-334M, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 9/24)
      - Legal Documents, Billing, Notes, and Correspondence: Case No. C81-334M, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Subseries D: Local Trial Board Charges, 1943-1991 (Box-folder 9/26-9/32)
      - Local Trial Board: Trial Against Munro Wilson, Other Trials, Executive Board and Trial Board Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1943-1963 (Box-folder 9/26)
      - Local Trial Board: Trial Against Munro Wilson, Other Trials, Executive Board and Trial Board Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1943-1963 (Box-folder 9/27)
      - Trial Board: Charges Against Walter Short by Members of Local 541, 1960-1960 (Box-folder 9/28)
      - Charges Against Lucius "Lucky" Jackson: Failure to Attend Executive Board Meetings, 1972-1972 (Box-folder 9/29)
      - Executive Board: Trial Board Case No. 8505-018: Restricting Rights of "Supervisors" in Shipscalers Union 541, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 9/30)
      - Anselmo Gaitan v. Local 541: Tort Defamation Claim: Trial Board Case No. 8505-015, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 9/31)
      - Executive Board Charges Against Agtuca, House, and Scott, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/32)
    - Subseries E: Van T. Harrison Legal Files, 1969-1984 (Box-folder 9/33-9/55)
      - Undated Signature Page for Trial Board Charges: Probably Against Van T. Harrison, 1969-1983 (Box-folder 9/33)
      - Financial Reporting: Correspondence Between International and Van T. Harrison, 1970-1970 (Box-folder 9/34)
      - Correspondence: Legal Representation and Billing, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 9/35)
      - Correspondence: Local 541 v. Van T. Harrison, 1972-1981 (Box-folder 9/36)
      - Legal Documents: Local 541 v. Van T. Harrison, 1972-1981 (Box-folder 9/37)
      - Notes, Statements, and Correspondence: Proof and Collection of Bonding Charges from Van T. Harrison, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 9/38)
      - Labor/Management Reporting: Administrative Audit: Charges Against Van T. Harrison, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 9/39)
      - U.S. District Court: Western District of Washington at Seattle: Case C79-739: Local 541 v. Van T. Harrison and International Union, 1979-1979 (Box-folder 9/40)
      - Bookkeeping for 1979: $12,000 Shortage, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 9/41)
      - Correspondence Regarding Charges Against Van T. Harrison and Election Challenge, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 9/42)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Bonding Claim Against Van T. Harrison, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 9/43)
      - Report of Special Hearings Panel: Retrial of Van T. Harrison, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 9/44)
      - National Labor Relations Board Case No. 19-CA-12820: Van T. Harrison v. Local 541, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 9/45)
      - Correspondence and Appeals/Hearing Documents: Charges Against Van T. Harrison, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 9/46)
      - Charges by Local 541 Against Van T. Harrison, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/47)
      - Correspondence from Nancy D. San Carlos to Local Executive Board: Charges Against Van T. Harrison, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/48)
      - Correspondence: Response from International Union Officers to Charges Against Van T. Harrison, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/49)
      - Transcript of Proceedings: Local 541 Trial Board: Hearing on Charges Brought Against Van T. Harrison, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/50)
      - Correspondence: Local's Response to Van T. Harrison's Appeal of Charges, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/51)
      - Van T. Harrison's Appeal of Charges, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 9/52)
      - Local 541 Trial Board: Appeal of Van Harrison, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 9/53)
      - Letter to Attorney General Regarding Status of Case Against Van T. Harrison et al., 1983-1983 (Box-folder 9/54)
      - Settlement of Bonding Claim Against Van T. Harrison, 1984-1984 (Box-folder 9/55)
    - Subseries F: Yvonne Quiroga Legal Files, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 9/56-10/6)
      - Correspondence, Legal Documents, and Notes: Quiroga v. Shipscalers: Case No. 81-2-15627-4, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 9/56)
      - Correspondence, Legal Documents, and Notes: Quiroga v. Shipscalers: Case No. 81-2-15627-4, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 9/57)
      - Salary Information and Legal Documents: Quiroga v. Shipscalers: Case No. 81-2-15627-4, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9/58)
      - Courtroom Exhibits Prepared by Yvonne Quiroga, 1979-1979 (Box-folder 9/59)
      - Trial Brief and Notes: Quiroga v. Shipscalers: Case No. 81-2-15627-4, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Legal Correspondence: Quiroga v. Shipscalers: Case No. 81-2-15627-4, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Legal Documents and Court Transcript: Volume I: Quiroga v. Shipscalers: King County Case No. 81-2-15627-4 (1 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Legal Documents and Court Transcript: Volume I: Quiroga v. Shipscalers: King County Case No. 81-2-15627-4 (2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Legal Documents and Court Transcript: Volume II: Quiroga v. Shipscalers: King County Case No. 81-2-15627-4 (1 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Legal Documents and Court Transcript: Volume II: Quiroga v. Shipscalers: King County Case No. 81-2-15627-4 (2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Subseries G: Member Death Records, 1946-1986 (Box-folder 10/7-10/11)
      - Member Deaths, 1946-1977 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Correspondence and Records: Deaths of Members (1 of 2), 1977-1986 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Correspondence and Records: Deaths of Members (2 of 2), 1977-1986 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Correspondence and Records: Deaths of Members (1 of 2), 1980-1986 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Correspondence and Records: Deaths of Members (2 of 2), 1980-1986 (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Subseries H: LaVerna Oliphant Legal Files, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - King County Superior Court Case No. 80-2-17947-1: Seattle Shipscalers Benevolent Corporation vs. LaVerna D. Oliphant: Deposition of L. Oliphant, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Subseries I: Legal Conflicts with Employers, 1965-1987 (Box-folder 10/13-10/20)
      - Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Company, 1965-1965 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - Lockheed Shipbuilding: Claims for Benefits: State Supreme Court Decision in Ancheta vs. Daly, 1967-1979 (Box-folder 10/14)
      - National Labor Relations Board Case No. 19-CA-13320: Lockheed Ship Builders and Construction Company, 1970-1981 (Box-folder 10/15)
      - King County Superior Court Case No. 81-2-04104-3: Cheryl A. Besk, et al., v. Todd Shipyard Corporation and Local 541: Sex Discrimination, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 10/16)
      - National Labor Relations Board Case No. 19-CA-14331: Mary Bingam v. Lockheed Ship Builders and Construction Company, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 10/17)
      - National Labor Relations Board Case Nos. 19-CA-13226; 19-CA-13298; 19-CA-13741; 19-CA-14066: Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Company, Electrical Workers Local 46, Boilermakers Local 104: Medical Screenings, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 10/18)
      - National Labor Relations Board Case No. 19-CA-15606: Mary Bingam v. Lockheed Ship Builders and Construction Company, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 10/19)
      - King County Superior Court Case No. 84-2-17468-4: Burruss, Bell, Davenport v. Complete Abrasive Blasting Systems, Inc. and McKinstry Company: Subpoena, Deposition, Correspondence, 1987-1987 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Subseries J: National Labor Relations Board Files, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 10/21-10/32)
      - National Labor Relations Board Charges Against Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Co.: Case No. 19-CA-11237, 1979-1979 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - National Labor Relations Board Decision: Pioneer Natural Gas Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union: Cases 16--CA--7968 and 16--CA--8691, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - National Labor Relations Board Decision: Case No. 19-CB-3868: Clydell Bates v. Local 541, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 10/23)
      - Legal Research: Department of Labor Charges: Northwest Employees Retirement Plan Trust Fund, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 10/24)
      - National Labor Relations Board: Decertification Request: Northwest Tank Service: Case No. 19-RD-1646, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 10/25)
      - National Labor Relations Board Case No. 19-CB-4424: John Somos v. Local 541, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 10/26)
      - National Labor Relations Board Case No. 19-CB-4564: Irenio J. Castro v. Local 541, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 10/27)
      - National Labor Relations Board: Case No. 19-CB-4538: J. Russell Stolsen v. Local 541: Charge Withdrawal, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 10/28)
      - National Labor Relations Board Case No. 19-CB-4538: J. Russell Stolsen v. Local 541, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 10/29)
      - National Labor Relations Board Case No. 19-CA-15366: Marine Power and Equipment: Failure to Process Grievances, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 10/30)
      - National Labor Relations Board Case No. 19-CB-4828: Clinton Edmonds v. Local 541, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 10/31)
      - National Labor Relations Board Charge Against Crosby and Overton, Inc. by Local 541: Failure to Bargain, 1985-1985 (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Subseries K: Arbitrations, 1951-1986 (Box-folder 10/33-10/39)
      - Arbitration: Rillera Termination, 1951-1980 (Box-folder 10/33)
      - Grievances and Memorandum of Understanding, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 10/34)
      - Grievance: Crosby and Overton: Isaac E. Williams Laid off out of seniority, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 10/35)
      - Arbitration Between Todd Pacific Shipyard Corporation and Ship Scalers Local No. 541, 1984-1984 (Box-folder 10/36)
      - Boilermakers Local No. 104: Arbitration v. Marine Power and Equipment Company, Inc.: John Vaux Discharge Grievance (1 of 3), 1985 (Box-folder 10/37)
      - Boilermakers Local No. 104: Arbitration v. Marine Power and Equipment Company, Inc.: John Vaux Discharge Grievance (2 of 3), 1985 (Box-folder 10/38)
      - Boilermakers Local No. 104: Arbitration v. Marine Power and Equipment Company, Inc.: John Vaux Discharge Grievance (3 of 3), 1985 (Box-folder 10/39)
    - Subseries L: Equal Employment Opportunity and Human Rights Commissions, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 10/40-10/44)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission and National Labor Relations Board Complaints: Discrimination: Ezell Ragsdale v. Todd Shipyards Corporation and Local 541, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 10/40)
      - Human Rights Commission Complaint #SEER-012108102: Frank E. Higdons v. Ship Scalers Local 541 and Red Barnes, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 10/41)
      - Correspondence and Documentation: Mary Bingham and Seattle Human Rights Department, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 10/42)
      - Equal Opportunity Employment Commission/Seattle Human Rights Department Complaint No. SHR83PEO74 and SHR82PE10: Mary Bingham v. Lockheed Marine, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 10/43)
      - Human Rights Commission Complaint #SHR82PE090: Cle Esther Lyons v. Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Company, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 10/44)
    - Subseries M: Jesse L. Washington Legal Files, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 11/1-11/27)
      - Wage Loss Plus Interest for Plaintiffs: Documentation and Totals: Amos, Chapman, Daniel, Daniel, Elmore, Hollingsworth, Kidd, Martin, Pearson, Sullivan, Washington, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 11/1)
      - U.S. Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit: Jesse L. Washington v. Local 541: Docket No. 80-3352: Appeals Documents, Notes, Deposition from Civil Action, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - Seattle District Court Case No. C74-240V, C74-240S, C74-2405: Legal Documents and Related Correspondence, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Legal Case File: U.S. District Court Western District of Washington at Seattle: Case No. C74-240S: Jesse L. Washington et al. vs. Northland Marine Co., Inc., et al., 1974 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - U.S. Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit: Jesse L. Washington v. Local 541: Docket Nos. 83-3850; 83-3851: Appeals Documents and Notes, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Affidavit of Forrest Hilton: Jesse Washington et al. vs. Northland Marine Co. Inc: United States District Court: Western District of Washington at Seattle: Case No. C74-240S, 1974 (Box-folder 11/6)
      - Notes, Correspondence, and Legal Documents: Jesse L. Washington v. Northland and Local 541; Local 541 v. Van T. Harrison, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Legal Case File: U.S. District Court Western District of Washington at Seattle: Case No. C74-240S: Jesse L. Washington et al. vs. Northland Marine Co., Inc., et al., 1975-1984 (Box-folder 11/8)
      - U.S. District Court Western District of Washington: Case No. C74-240S: Jesse L. Washington, et al. v. Northland Marine Lines, Inc., et al.: Legal Documents, 1975 (Box-folder 11/9)
      - Legal Case File: U.S. District Court Western District of Washington at Seattle: Case No. C74-240S: Jesse L. Washington et al. vs. Northland Marine Co., Inc., et al., 1976 (Box-folder 11/10)
      - U.S. District Court Western District of Washington Case No. C74-240S: Jesse L. Washington v. Ship Scalers Local No. 412, et al.: Transcript of Proceedings, 1979 (Box-folder 11/11)
      - Legal Case File: U.S. District Court Western District of Washington at Seattle: Case No. C74-240S: Jesse L. Washington et al. vs. Northland Marine Co., Inc., et al., 1979 (Box-folder 11/12)
      - Legal Case File: U.S. District Court Western District of Washington at Seattle: Case No. C74-240S: Jesse L. Washington et al. vs. Northland Marine Co., Inc., et al., 1980 (Box-folder 11/13)
      - Seattle District Court Case No. C74-240S(V): Docketing Statements and Appellants' Reply Brief, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 11/14)
      - Seattle District Court Case No. C74-204V: Jessie L. Washington et al. v. Local 541: Defendant's Memorandum on Damages and Attorney's Fees, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 11/15)
      - Seattle District Court Case No. C74-240V, C74-240S, C81-334M: Legal Documents, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 11/16)
      - Seattle District Court Case No. C74-240S: Legal Documents, 1982 (Box-folder 11/17)
      - Seattle District Court Case No. C74-240V, C74-240S, C81-334M: Legal Documents and Press, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 11/18)
      - Correspondence: Fidelity Bond #553 13 49--Case #C74-204V, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 11/19)
      - Damages and Bonding Claims: Jesse L. Washington v. Local 541, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 11/20)
      - Jesse L. Washington v. Local 541 and Northland Marine Co., Inc.: Legal Documents, Correspondence, and Notes (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 11/21)
      - Jesse L. Washington v. Local 541 and Northland Marine Co., Inc.: Legal Documents, Correspondence, and Notes (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 11/22)
      - Seattle District Court Case No. C74-240S: Judgment and Related Correspondence, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 11/23)
      - Seattle District Court Case No. C74-240S: Settlement Proposal, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 11/24)
      - Seattle District Court Case No. C74-240S(V): Legal Correspondence and Syllabus of Similar Case: DelCostello v. Teamsters, 1983 (Box-folder 11/25)
      - Legal Research: Jesse L. Washington v. Local 541, 1983 (Box-folder 11/26)
      - Seattle District Court Case No. C74-240V: Final Settlement and Related Correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 11/27)
    - Subseries N: Rex Ricardo, Jr. Legal Files, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 11/28-11/29)
      - Financial Discrepancies and Court Case: Ship Scalers Local 541 vs. Rex Ricardo, Jr., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 11/28)
      - Legal Documents: Attorney L. Presley Gill Regarding Case with Rex Ricardo, Jr., 1958-1965 (Box-folder 11/29)
    - Subseries O: Robert "Bob" Barnes Legal Files, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 11/30-11/36)
      - Grievance and Employment Security Department Case: Robert Allen Barnes v. Lockheed Shipyard, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 11/30)
      - Legal Research: Department of Labor Charges: Brock v. Barnes, et al.: Northwest Employees Retirement Plan Trust Fund (1 of 2), 1980-1986 (Box-folder 11/31)
      - Legal Research: Department of Labor Charges: Brock v. Barnes, et al.: Northwest Employees Retirement Plan Trust Fund (2 of 2), 1980-1986 (Box-folder 11/32)
      - U.S. District Court Western District of Washington: Civil Action No. C-83-1222 V: Brock v. Barnes et al.: Legal Documents and Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 11/33)
      - U.S. District Court Western District of Washington Case No. C83-12222V: Deposition of Robert Allen Barnes, 1984-1984 (Box-folder 11/34)
      - Charges Against President Robert Coan and Secretary-Treasurer Robert Barnes by Members Colleen Christensen and John Scannell: Breach of Fiduciary Responsibility: Seattle District Court Case No. C86-1027, 1986-1986 (Box-folder 11/35)
      - U.S. District Court Western District of Washington: Civil Action No. C-83-1222 V: Brock v. Barnes et al.: Legal Documents, 1986-1986 (Box-folder 11/36)
  - Series VII: Member Files, 1944-1986 (Box-folder 12/1-12/44; 16/9; 12/45-14/246)
    Restricted
    - Subseries A: Non-Alphabetized or Multi-Member Files, 1951-1986 (Box-folder 12/1-12/44; 16/9)
      - Applications for Retired Medical Benefits; Member Termination Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Member Work and Insurance Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1984-1984 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 12/5)